#### Contact

SADARPUR COLONY SEC 45 NOIDA 08287969210 (Work) vishal.kmehra.642@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vishal642 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

React.js JavaScript GatsbyJS

### Certifications

Certification in Front end Development

# Vishal Mehra

React JS | Next.Js | Front End | Node | Express | Javascript Developer

110091

## Summary

Coding on React JS and dreaming on React JS . Help companies to build complex web applications serving 1,000,000+ users with React and modern technologies. I specialize in JavaScript and have professional experience working with React.js, Gatsby JS & Next.js .

## Experience

hiringplug™ Software Developer January 2022 - Present (7 months) Delhi. India

Bytequests software Pvt Itd React Developer October 2021 - January 2022 (4 months) Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

https://www.tomedes.com

- Built application with 1000k+ active users from scratch.
- Developing Frontend and logical UI for Tomedes translation Services.

Tech Altum
Frontend Web Developer
December 2020 - September 2021 (10 months)
Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

### Education

Maharaja agrseen college Bca, Computer Science · (August 2020 - July 2023)

Tech Altum

Diploma in Front end development, Computer Science